♪ 我的站到了 ♪
♪ This is my stop ♪
♪ 得下车了 ♪
♪ Got to get off ♪
♪ 还敢更挤嘛 ♪
♪ I might go pop ♪
借过
Excuse me
♪ 原谅我这么直 ♪
♪ I've got to be direct ♪
♪ 如冒犯请指教 ♪
♪ If I'm off, please correct ♪
♪ 你挡着我道了 ♪
♪ You're standing on my neck ♪
拽妹Daria
漫迪字幕组&@Daria拽妹黛薇儿
——·@严肃活泼小kk译制·——
大家好 我们是神秘螺旋
Hello. We're Mystik Spiral.
不过我们将会改名
But we might change our name.
♪ 看到你幸灾乐祸我是如此欣慰 ♪
♪ I'm glad you're happy watching my pain, ♪
♪ 燃烧在我灵魂深处谷物堆里的麦田圈 ♪
♪ burning crop circles on my soul's waves of grain. ♪
♪ 我们没有风花雪月 但你却直截了当 ♪
♪ We had no love scene but you've cut to the chase, ♪
♪ 你砍下我的鼻子以示泄愤 ♪
♪ you're chopping off my nose to spite my face. ♪
♪ 噢 我的鼻子 噢 我的脸庞 ♪
♪ Ow, my nose! Ow, my face! ♪
♪ Ow, my nose! Ow, my face! Ow... ♪
弄完这事后想去吃汉堡吗?
You want to go for a burger after this?
啊?
What?
等下想去吃汉堡吗?
You want to go for a burger after this?
啊?
What?
汉堡 吃 吃汉堡
Burger! Get! Get burger!
吃汉堡? 也行
Get burger? Hmm... okay.
这地方的确让我肉欲焚身
This place does put me in the mood for meat.
好极了 我去告诉Trent我们也去
Cool. I'll tell Trent we're going with him.
和... Trent一起?
With... Trent?
嗯 乐队要去簇群汉堡店
Yeah, the band's going over to Cluster Burger.
你不会手足无措得像个白痴吧?
You're not going to act like a complete nitwit, are you?
定位精准
Define complete.
我只想去上个厕所
Um, I just need to go to the bathroom.
机智 看看哪里脱妆
Good idea. Check your lack of makeup.
厕所是你的了 亲
All yours, dude.
我受不了啦 我到底在想什么?
I can't stand this. What was I thinking?
Brittany?
好呗 Kevin就是个愚蠢自私又自傲的混蛋
All right, so Kevin is a stupid, selfish, conceited jerk.
他总比那Terry还是Jerry还是随便叫啥的人和这白痴俱乐部强
He's still better than Terry or Jerry or whatever his name is and this stupid club.
Terry和Jerry是谁?
Who's Terry or Jerry?
噢不 我说太多了
Oh, no! I've said too much!
你脖子怎么了?
What happened to your neck?
你的脖子 它起水泡了
Your neck. It's all, like, blotchy.
我不造
I don't know.
我丝毫不惊讶你在这破地方会染上什么恶疾
I'm not surprised you could catch something in a horrible place like this.
Brittany 你能帮个忙么?
Uh, Brittany, could you do me a favor?
行吧?
Um... yes?
和Jane说我得走了?
Find Jane and tell her I had to leave?
行 不过...
Sure, but...
能答应我不告诉Kevin那Terry或Jerry还是嘛玩意的事么?
will you promise not to tell Kevin about Terry or Jerry or whoever?
这情况不太可能发生 虽然可能会出些奇怪的漏子
In the unlikely event that, through some bizarre set of circumstances,
我不和Kevin讲话了
I end up conversing with Kevin,
我不会和他说Terry或Jerry的事
I won't tell him about Terry or Jerry.
谢啦
Thanks!
Daria? 你在里面吗?
Daria? You in there?
别担心
Don't worry.
考虑下女性隐私好嘛 拜托
Have some consideration for female modesty, please!
噢 好的 抱歉
Oh, sure. Sorry.
我会告诉Jane的
I'll tell Jane.
我不会告诉Kevin的
I won't tell Kevin.
紧急事故? 对 没错
Emergency. Yes, that is correct.
Daria
Daria!
走吧
Let's go.
去哪?
Where to?
是什么让一个阳光 活泼 合群的青少年
What makes a happy, vibrant, involved teen
变得粗暴 易怒 孤僻?
become a surly, resentful, withdrawn teen?
就是嘛 是什么?
Yeah, what?
毒品 归根结底
Drugs, that's what.
老生常谈的事袭击了新生代
The old story hits a new generation.
Daria 是你吗?
Daria, is that you?
嗯 嗨 晚安
Yeah, hi, good night.
噢天啊 Helen 你绝不觉得Daria她...
Oh, my gosh, Helen, you don't think Daria...
Jake 她本来就不阳光不活泼不合群
Jake, she was never happy, vibrant or involved.
另外 她是个全优生
Besides, she's a straight-A student.
那可能是她装的
That could be her cover!
她的药 我们得检查她的药
Her pupils, we should check her pupils.
我那小册子扔哪了?
What did I do with that pamphlet?
Jake 拜托
Jake, please.
我们都晓得 她和周玛丽在娱乐室瞎混
For all we know, she's dealing Mary Jo out of the rec room.
那是简玛丽 而且我们没有娱乐室
That's Mary Jane, and we don't have a rec room.
卡莱尔商场今天内裤和百吉饼打折哟
It's briefs and bagels day at the Carlyle.
Daria 我想和你谈谈
Daria, I wanted to talk to you about something.
你看过这小册子么?
Have you seen this pamphlet?
"你的小孩是否在吸毒? 十项预警信号"
"Is Your Teenager Using Drugs? Ten Warning Signs."
是 是 不是 可能是 有时候 嗯
Yes. Yes. No. Maybe. Sometimes. Hmm.
一周大概三次
About three times a week.
除非她尽量避免的话
And not if she can possibly avoid it.
在我看来 Quinn很正常
In my opinion, Quinn's clean.
啊?
What?
虽然你可能想查她的药
Although you might want to check her pupils.
我 嗯 我是在怀疑你 Daria
I, uh, was thinking more about you, Daria.
噢 那你就不应该让我看这个
Oh, then you're not supposed to let me read this.
你应该悄悄滴暗中监视我
You're supposed to sneak around,
搜搜我放袜子的抽屉
spying on me and looking through my sock drawer.
孩纸 你袜子放在哪个抽屉?
Kiddo, which one is your sock drawer?
我知道是哪个 爹地
I can show you, Daddy.
看看是谁呀 透明姑娘
Well, look who it is. Invisible girl.
瞧 昨晚的事我很抱歉
Look, I'm sorry about last night
算了吧
Aw, forget it.
和Brittany去垃圾摇滚俱乐部玩的确是一个很难得的机会
It was a rare opportunity, getting to hang out with Brittany in a grunge club.
尽管她头发都要甩到我鞋里了
Although her hair did leak onto my shoes.
你确定那不是她的脑子?
You're sure that wasn't her brain?
不 甩进来的东西太大
No, there was too much of it.
是啥让你得了这所谓的皮疹?
Any idea what caused this so-called rash?
我也想知道
I wish I knew.
不管咋说 重点是你没有向朋友求助
Anyway, the important thing is that instead of going to your friends for help,
你大呼小叫地溜走了
you ran screaming into the night.
差不多
Basically.
完全合乎逻辑
Perfectly logical response.
我也觉得
I thought so.
傲慢 自大 自负... 凶残
Arrogant, proud, vain... thuggish.
李尔王完全有过之无不及
King Lear is all of these and worse.
可是 如果我们把自己象征性的脑袋转到另一边去斜视呢
And yet, if we tilt our figurative head to the side and squint just so,
他是不是有一点儿... 可爱?
isn't he also just a little... cuddly?
是什么让暴君如此...
What is it about tyrants that makes them so...
我不知道 是魅力吗?
I don't know, charismatic?
我们独一无二的李校长... Daria 噢亲爱的
Our own Ms. Li... Daria? Oh, dear.
也许我该问问是不是有人想出去
Perhaps I should ask if anyone else might wish to be excused
因为今天的主题带来的敏感情绪
because of the emotionally sensitive nature of today's subject matter.
真恶心
Eww! Gross!
这镇上有没有我遇不到熟人的厕所?
Is there a bathroom in this town without someone I know in it?
你的脸咋了?
What happened to your face?
我不知道 是皮疹吧
I don't know. It's a rash or something.
没事 别害怕 我这应该有什么药能用上
Okay, don't panic. I'm sure I have something here.
看看 芦荟保湿霜
Let's see, moisturizing cream with aloe.
现在涂也没治
Too late for that.
这有支水疗八号 终极痘立消
Well, there's hydro-eight, the ultimate pimple medicine,
不过你脸上那不是什么痘痘 我猜
except that's not really pimples, I guess.
什么情况 你是真的在帮我么?
I don't get it. You're really helping me?
护肤危机大于性格不和 Daria
Skin-care crises transcend personality conflicts, Daria.
是时尚俱乐部的宗旨
It's in the fashion club bylaws.
而且这显然是场危机
And this is obviously a crisis.
这是给小瑕疵用的修复露
Now, this is poxicil for non-specific blemishes,
这个是给小痘痘用的痘立停
and this is salosocilin for a micro-zit condition.
我不觉得那些是我要的
I don't really think any of those are what I need.
嗯 该来点厉害的药
Yeah. It's time for some serious prescriptions.
嘿 你用那堆东西来干嘛?
Hey, what are you doing with all that stuff?
你皮肤挺好
Your skin's fine.
而且一直都会这么好
And it's going to stay that way.
对不起啦 俺帮不上忙 再见
Well, sorry I can't help. Bye.
Jake 亲爱的 我们有麻烦了
Jake, honey, we have a problem.
Daria在校医室里
Daria is in the school nurse's office.
噢我的神啊 怎么了?
Oh, my God, what is it?
他们是不是查出什么了?
What did they find on her?
就告诉我现在治疗还来得及吧
Just tell me it's not too late for rehab!
Jake 懂点事?
Oh, Jake, will you get a grip?
她得了皮疹 他们想让她立刻去看医生
She has a rash and they want her to see a doctor right away.
皮疹 皮疹...
Rashes, rashes...
我让Marianne找Davidson医生了
I had Marianne call Dr. Davidson,
问题是 我有个大会要开...
but the thing is, I've got this big Calco meeting...
我能赶到学校... 11分钟内
I can be at the school in... 11 minutes.
皮疹... 算了 没时间
Rashes... never mind, no time now.
该死
Damn it!
去死吧 你这鲁莽的蠢货
Go to hell, you reckless bastard!
我孩子得皮疹了 这破窗是关的
My kid's got a rash! Ah, the damn window's up!
我说 去死吧 你这鲁莽的... 嘿 等等 回来
I said, go to hell, you reckless... hey, wait, get back here!
Daria 我假定你枕头内衬里不含任何人造纤维吧
Daria, I assume the inner lining of your pillow doesn't contain any synthetic fibers.
好吧
Um, okay.
你不喝碳酸饮料吧?
You don't drink carbonated beverages, do you?
不喝
Yes.
你不吃含人造色素 漂白剂 面粉 精制糖的食物吧?
Do you stay away from foods with artificial colors, bleach, flour and refined sugar?
不吃 我到底得了什么?
No. What have I got?
我不清楚
I haven't the slightest idea.
可能是某种过敏
Probably some kind of allergy
可不能排除一些更... 严重的
but we can't rule out something a bit more... serious.
特别是你还有低烧
Especially with the slight fever you're running.
只是为了安全着想
Just to be on the safe side,
我希望你到医院做些检查
I'd like to check you into the hospital for some tests.
不是吧
No way.
好了 新被单都铺好了
There you go. Nice, fresh sheets, and all tucked in.
你压根不造可怜的Sullivan太太刚还躺在这 然后...
You'd never know that poor Mrs. Sullivan just lay here and...
谁?
Who?
没谁 谁都没有 明天见
Nobody, no one. See you tomorrow.
老爸 老爸
Dad. Dad!
你好像很渴 要不要喝点苏打?
You look thirsty. Why don't you go get a soda?
这有水 我不想离开你
Oh, there's water here. I don't want to leave you.
去吧 爸爸 我好着呢
Go ahead, Dad. I'll be fine.
给自己来罐美滋滋的根汁汽水... 要冰冻的
Treat yourself to a nice root beer... in a frosty cold can.
根汁汽水是含二氧化碳和糖的无酒精饮料 如沙士
冰冻的...
Frosty cold can...
你懂哒 我不介意来罐根汁 你要不要也来一罐 小鬼?
you know, I wouldn't mind a root beer! How about you, kiddo?
我不喝 去吧去吧
I'm fine. Go on, now.
去去就回
Be right back.
哟
Yo!
嗨
Hi.
嗨 你在哪?
Hi. Where are you?
医院
The hospital.
啊?
What?
就待一两晚 他们要搞点检查
Just for a night or two, while they run some tests.
真倒霉
Bummer.
没啥的 不过呢
It's no big deal, but the thing is,
我希望你不会和任何人说我得了皮疹
I'd rather you didn't tell anybody about this rash.
再联系
I'll call you back.
噢 亲爱的 我的老天哟 看看你
Oh, sweetie. Oh, my goodness, just look at you.
嗨老妈 我也很高兴见到你 老爸去喝苏打了
Hi, Mom. Good to see you, too. Dad's getting a soda.
Jake 你看到她的脸了么?医生怎么说?
Jake, have you seen her face? What did the doctor say?
还没人来给她看诊呢 不过Davidson医生说不是毒品问题
No one's been in to see her yet, but Dr. Davidson doesn't think it's drugs.
没人来给她看诊你就溜去喝苏打了?
No one's been in to see her, and you're going out for sodas?!
Jake 你特么就能不能老老实实地处理一次情况?
Jake, can't you take charge of a situation for one damn minute?
- 可我... - 嗨Daria
- But I... - Hi, Daria.
嗨 Quinn
Hi, Quinn.
你要是有脑子你就晓得
If you had any sense you'd realize
这些大医院总是忽视病人
that these big hospitals let patients slip through the cracks all the time.
你得时刻盯紧他们
You have to keep after them every second.
你造吗 正是这种不消停的争吵
You know, this is exactly the kind of constant bickering
才会导致一个阳光少年吸毒
that could make an otherwise happy young person turn to drugs.
我现在就要一个医生
I want a doctor in here now!
我干嘛要费劲?
Oh, why do I bother?
护士... 护士... 护士
Nurse... nurse... nurse!
是你说我能喝汽水的
You said I could have a root beer.
Jane?
Brittany? 你的头发怎么了?
Brittany? What happened to your hair?
别管那个 你看到... Daria了吗?
Never mind that now. Have you seen... Daria?
你为毛会想找... Daria?
Why would you want... Daria?
你为毛会觉得我想找她?
What makes you think I want her?
我不找她 谁说我要找她了
I don't want her. Who said I want her.
你问我有没有看到她嘛
You asked me if I'd seen her.
她没和你说什么我的趣事吧?
She hasn't told you anything... interesting about me, has she?
压根没人和我说过你的什么趣事
No one's ever told me anything interesting about you.
那就好
That's a relief.
怎么说 她一两天后就回来了
Anyway, she'll be back in a day or two.
她在医院里让医生给她检查罕见的... 罕见的情况
She's in the hospital while they check out that ra... rare condition.
情况?
Condition?
嗯 她得了轻微的脑热
Yeah, she's come down with a slight case of, um, brain fever.
一种书呆子会得的病
It's a thing that brains get.
哇 听起来可严重
Wow, that sounds serious.
不 不 通常你读本销场书的话就会好的
No, no, usually if you just read a best-seller it'll go away.
所以呢 没必要和别人说
So, um, no need to mention it to anyone.
我会转告她你的问候
I'll tell her you asked about her.
就问她记不记得我们的约定
Just ask her if she remembers our deal.
什么约定?
What deal?
什么什么约定?
就你刚说的约定呀
The deal you just mentioned.
我才没说什么约定呢 忘了我说的约定
I didn't say anything about a deal. Forget I said anything about a deal.
忘了我说的住院
Forget I said anything about a hospital.
好的
Okay!
嘿 现在我们有约定了啊
Hey! Now we have a deal.
什么约定?
What deal?
回见
Later.
脑热...
Brain fever...
死神穿着天鹅绒般的绿色
Death wore velvety green.
接下来《呕心小世界: 杀人的家庭植物》
Homicidal house plants, next on Sick, Sad World.
"玩忽职守"这词一定涵盖什么意义
The word malpractice must still have some meaning.
Morgendorffer太太 我向您保证...
Mrs. Morgendorffer, I assure you...
这不是Sullivan夫人的房间么?
Wasn't this Mrs. Sullivan's room?
谁?
Who?
算了 你怎么样啦 Daria? 我是Phillips医生
Never mind. How are you doing, Daria? I'm Dr. Phillips.
你好
Hello.
嗨 我是Quinn 我也病了
Hi, I'm Quinn. I get sick, too.
你好 Quinn
Hello, Quinn.
我觉得你救死扶伤实在是酷极了
I think the way you save peoples' lives is really cool.
谢谢
Thank you.
Daria 待会会有人来给你抽血
Daria, they'll be coming by in a few minutes to take a little blood.
除了皮疹 还有哪里不舒服么?
Besides this rash, is there anything else that's been bothering you?
她还抽鼻子
She's been sniffling.
我猜她是过敏了 不过她坚称没有
I think she may have allergies but she insists she doesn't.
抽鼻子? 那小册子去哪了?
Sniffling? Where's that pamphlet?
Jake 起来让医生坐
Jake, get up and let the doctor sit down.
不用不用 没关系
No, no, no, that's all right.
事实上呢 如果你们不介意出去一会儿
Actually, if you all wouldn't mind leaving the room for a moment,
我有些私人问题想问Daria
there are a couple of rather personal questions I'd like to ask Daria.
好的
Of course.
不用费心啦 她啥都没干
Don't bother. She hasn't done anything.
你也是 Morgendorffer太太
You, too, Mrs. Morgendorffer.
哦... 好吧
Oh... all right.
简而言之
Let's make this short.
我不吸毒也不乱性
I don't use drugs and I'm not sexually active.
不 你当然不
No, of course not.
你的"当然不"什么意思?
What do you mean, "of course not"?
我的意思是 你说是就是
I mean, if you say so.
那你是要问什么?
So then, what did you want to ask me?
没啥特别的
Nothing in particular.
我只是想你能摆脱父母一会儿
I just thought you could use a break from your parents for a while.
你玩金罗美纸牌么?
You play gin rummy?
玩
Sure.
实际上 我是要问你一件事?
Actually, I did want to ask you one thing.
嗯?
Yeah?
你妈怎么回事?
What is it with your mother?
你是谁?
Who are you?
我是Eleanor Sullivan 这是我的房间
I am Eleanor Sullivan. This is my room.
一定是出错了
There must be some kind of mistake.
服务台在大厅
The nurses' station is down the hall.
Eleanor Sullivan? Sullivan夫人?
Eleanor Sullivan? Mrs. Sullivan?
你别害怕 我才害怕呢
You mustn't be frightened. I was frightened.
特别是那些最后的痛苦
Especially during those final agonies, ohhh!
不过那是我知道我得去哪之前的事了 跟我来
But that was before I knew where I was going. Come.
我们去哪?
Where are we going?
亲爱的 你不知道么?
My dear, don't you know?
这是天堂吗?
Is this Heaven?
它有很多名字
Mmm, it has many names.
很漂亮
It's beautiful.
对
Yes.
嘿 咋地捏? 你想来派对么?
Hey, what's up? You wanna party?
什么?
Excuse me?
嘿 宝贝 你干嘛不把眼镜摘下来放放松?
Hey, babe, why don't you take your glasses off and relax?
我已经很放松了
Um, I'm plenty relaxed.
从我沉着有节奏的呼吸声中你就能知道
You can tell by my deep, rhythmic breathing.
亲 你干了什么呀? 又带了一个书呆子来?
Oh, man, what'd you do? Bring us another brain?
听着 我只是去他们要我去的地方
Look, I just go where they tell me.
有问题吗?
Um, is there a problem?
这里是天堂 亲爱的
This is Heaven, sweetheart.
我们要书呆子干嘛?
What would we want with a brain?
我不...
I don't...
抱歉
Sorry.
宝贝 你头发怎么了?
Babe, what happened to your hair?
现在别管那个
Never mind that now.
你造Daria得了脑热吗?
Did you know that Daria has brain fever?
脑热?
Brain fever?
嗯 是不是听起来超严重的?
Yeah. Doesn't that sound serious?
你去弄把手术刀
You get the scalpel.
我们能用我爸的谷仓作手术室
We can use my dad's barn as an operating room.
你爸才没有谷仓呢
Your dad doesn't have a barn.
我们能用你的地下室
We could use your basement.
Brittany 我确定要是很严重的话 Daria要住院了
Brittany, I'm sure if it was serious, Daria would be in the hospital.
啊? 她住院了?
What? She is in the hospital?
她才没住院
She's not in the hospital.
我答应我不能说关于住院的事
I promised I wouldn't say anything about the hospital
因为我和Daria有约了
because I made a deal with Daria
她遵守她的 我遵守我的
and she kept her part and I kept my part
然后我和Jane也约定了
but then I made another deal with Jane
约好了我才知道我是在做约定
and I didn't even know I was making it until it was made
现在我违反承诺了 因为我说了医院的事
and now I didn't keep my part because I told about the hospital
所以现在Jane要去揭发我的事
so now Jane's going to tell about the deal
然而我还没说是什么意思呢
and I didn't mean anything by it
我只想看看晚上不做运动的小孩都在干嘛
I just wanted to see what other kids do at night who don't do sports
他一点都不重要 Kevvy 我发誓
and he didn't mean anything to me, Kevvy, I swear it!
所以... 她是住院了咯
So... she is in the hospital.
对于抽血的事我很抱歉 Daria
I'm sorry about all this blood work, Daria,
不过目前为止一切都好
but so far, all signs are good.
你是说除了我差点变成红烧番茄脸
Other than my having turned into Ms. Tomato Head, you mean.
嗯
Well, yeah.
嗨
Hi.
嘿
Hey.
Jane 这是Philips医生
Jane, this is Dr. Phillips.
很高兴见到你 你是朋友 不是家人吧?
Pleased to meet you. Friend, not family, right?
你咋知道?
How can you tell?
Daria显得很高兴 我待会再过来
Daria seemed happy to see you. I'll stop by later.
好的 谢啦
Okay, thanks.
哎哟哟 医生 人家痛痛
Ooh-la-la. Doctor, I have a pain.
拜托 那货是屠夫
Please. The man is a butcher.
瞧他对我的脸做的好事
Look what he's done to my face.
很红嘛 到底咋回事?
That's pretty red. Um, what is it?
目前为止 所有测试都呈阴性 所以可能啥事都没有
So far, the tests are all negative, so probably nothing.
好像我需要这个
Like I need this.
哪个?
What?
一个爬满皮肤的发光诡异大疹子
A big, bright mysterious rash covering my skin.
我造啦
I know!
你在这很好地远离他人性格上的孤僻
And here you were, perfectly capable of alienating people on personality alone.
你懂的 你可以只送花来
You know, you could have just sent flowers.
嘿 也没那么糟嘛
Hey, it's not so bad.
都会消下去的 今年要没好的话明年肯定会好
And it'll go away, if not this year, then definitely next.
至少学校里没人看到
At least no one at school has seen it.
他们可能都没意识到我不在呢
They probably haven't even noticed I'm gone.
Daria?
Brittany? 你在这干嘛?
Brittany? What are you doing here?
我只是想谢谢你没有打破我们的约定
Um, I just wanted to thank you for not going back on our deal,
而且我猜我能在这找到Jane
and I thought I might find Jane here
告诉她我有点食言了
and tell her I did kind of go back on our deal,
不过我同样有点对我俩的约定食言
but I also kind of went back on your part of our deal
所以你就没必要食言啦
so there's no use in you doing that.
我们有约定么?
We had a deal?
另外来看看你怎么样了 你可真红
And to see how you were. Um, you're kind of red.
嗯 不过我应该还行
Yes, but I'm probably okay.
太棒啦
Great!
我们到底约了什么?
What was our deal?
Daria?
你来干嘛?
What are you doing here?
Brittany说你得了什么脑热
Well, Brittany said you had some brain fever or something,
可你不在医院
but you weren't in the hospital.
所以我就继续问Jane
So I kept asking Jane,
她最后承认你得了皮疹而且住院了
and she finally admitted you had a rash and you were in the hospital.
所以我们就想自己过来看看 你怎么样了
So we just figured we'd come down here and see for ourselves, how you were.
我应该还不错吧...
I'm probably okay...
那就好
So that's cool.
...对人型龙虾来说
... for a human lobster.
噢 那你是有点红嘛
Oh, so you're a little red.
每个人都有机会得皮疹的
It could happen to anybody.
很多人都会得的
Well, it could happen to lots of people.
Daria?
Quinn?
- 你怎样啦? - 噢 我...
- How are you? - Oh, I'm...
那个Philips医生今天还来不来? 我... 我好痛噢
Is that Dr. Phillips coming by today? I've got, um, a twinge.
Daria?
Kevin?
你来干嘛?
What are you doing here?
我去了Mack家 地下室没人
I went over to Mack's house and, like, the basement was empty.
Daria 看到你我很开心哟
Daria, am I glad to see you.
谢谢 Kevin
Um, thanks, Kevin.
我很担心他们要抛弃我来做手术
I was afraid they'd start the operation without me.
说来话长
It's a long story.
等你恢复精神我再告诉你
Maybe later, when you have your strength back.
Daria?
你是谁?
Who are you?
我是Sullivan 我是不是忘了个灌肠袋在这儿?
I'm Mrs. Sullivan. Did I leave an enema bag here?
Philips医生非常好
Dr. Phillips was very nice.
他说Daria的皮疹可能是焦虑造成的
He said Daria's rash was probably triggered by anxiety.
他给我们开了处方 以防疹子不会自己消退
He gave us a prescription in case it doesn't go away on its own.
焦虑? 什么会让你焦虑 亲爱的?
Anxiety? Well, what could be giving you anxiety, sweetie?
想想啊 我生活中的每时每处?
Um, let's see. Every aspect of my life?
那是Jane 我走啦
That's Jane. See you.
Daria?
嗯?
Yeah?
你爹和我只想让你知道
Your father and I just want you to know
我们为你处理这事的态度感到骄傲
we're very proud of the way you handled this situation.
没错 小宝贝
That's right, kiddo.
我除了傻坐着等他们抽血以外什么都没做
I didn't do anything but sit there like a crash dummy while they took blood.
你们很担心 对吗?
You were worried, weren't you?
Daria 我们是家长
Daria, we're your parents.
嗯 是...
Yeah, well...
谢谢你们的陪伴
Thanks for being there for me.
她刚才是不是说...?
Did she just say...?
Jake 别坏了气氛
Jake, don't spoil the moment.
嘿 准备走啦?
Hey, ready to go?
嗯
Yeah.
Trent来接我们
Trent's going to give us a ride.
Trent?
嘿 Daria
Hey, Daria.
干嘛?
What?
欢迎微博关注
@漫迪字幕组